prepaidmeters.co.za 2019-06-17

# Prepaid Meters - Our Privacy Policy

We recognise the importance of protecting your personal information. As such we subscribe to the principles, outlined in Section 51 of the [Electronic Communications and Transactions Act 2002](http://www.internet.org.za/ect_act.html) that governs your right to having your personal information kept private.

We define personal information as all information specific to yourself that you provide to us over the Internet or any other channel. This includes personal data that you provide to us when you register to purchase products, subscribe to our newsletter, register as an affiliate, post a support ticket or just a question you asked via e-mail.

We have the highest regard for the privacy of our subscribers and will use personal information only as appropriate in the normal course of business to provide the products and services you have requested.

We do not and will not sell or provide personal information to third parties for independent use.

We value the information that you choose to provide us and will therefore take reasonable steps to protect your personal information from loss, misuse or unauthorised alteration.

The information we maintain concerning our [customers](http://www.prepaidmeters.co.za/component/seoglossary/6-prepaid-online-vending/customer "<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Used in reference to the Natural or Juristic person who is considered the owner of the meter. The customer is the person who has the direct relationship with the company and under whose instruction the company acts.</span></p>") and [consumers](http://www.prepaidmeters.co.za/component/seoglossary/6-prepaid-online-vending/consumer "<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Used in reference to the Natural or Juristic person who is typically required to purchase, load and use utilities. The consumer does not have a direct relationship with the company. The consumer has a direct relationship with our customer and an indirect relationship with the company. The company does not take instruction from the consumer.</span></p>") is stored in databases that have built-in safeguards to ensure the privacy and confidentiality of that information.
